<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo Themes</title>
    <link>https://clearbear.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugo Themes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2008 - 2014, all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 15:08:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://clearbear.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t fap, ever.	</title>
      <link>https://clearbear.netlify.com/post/notfap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 15:08:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://clearbear.netlify.com/post/notfap/</guid>
      <description>If you want to live a happy life, don&amp;rsquo;t fap. Fapping makes us lose interest in life. It destroys our life force, the semen. Think about it, semen helps create human beings, and if you save the thing that can create the most powerful species on the entire universe, you will create that species inside of your self, your own body.
The humans that are created with semen are capable of everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to not relapse or fail during a no fap streak</title>
      <link>https://clearbear.netlify.com/post/win/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 15:48:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://clearbear.netlify.com/post/win/</guid>
      <description>In order to not relapse during our no fap journey, we have to practice handling pressure. Pressure can be of urges or just any negative thoughts or sadness, boredom. Too much of urges or anxiety draws us into peeking, thinking that it will solve our anxiety, boredom or urges and we will be happy. The mind tricks us into thinking that by fulfilling our peeking and PMOing desire, we will be fulfilled and happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help</title>
      <link>https://clearbear.netlify.com/post/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 15:40:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://clearbear.netlify.com/post/help/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s always better to take God&amp;rsquo;s help in our no fap journey. God can help solve all our problems. Therefore, connect with God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clear</title>
      <link>https://clearbear.netlify.com/post/clear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 13:56:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://clearbear.netlify.com/post/clear/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m using vim and hugo to generate this site. The theme is after dark. Thanks. Yeah, this is actually great.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>